(CHEERFUL POP MUSIC)
♪ OH ♪
♪ OH OH ♪
♪ OH YEAH ♪
♪ YOU HAVE SO MANY
RELATIONSHIPS IN THIS LIFE ♪
♪ ONLY ONE OR TWO WILL LAST ♪
♪ YOU GO THROUGH ALL
THE PAIN AND STRIFE ♪
♪ THEN YOU TURN YOUR BACK
AND THEY'RE GONE SO FAST ♪
♪ OH YEAH ♪
♪ AND THEY'RE GONE
SO FAST, YEAH ♪
♪ OH, SO HOLD ON TO THE
ONES WHO REALLY CARE ♪
♪ IN THE END THEY'LL BE
THE ONLY ONES THERE ♪
♪ AND WHEN YOU GET OLD AND
START LOSING YOUR HAIR ♪
♪ CAN YOU TELL ME
WHO WILL STILL CARE ♪
♪ OH YEAH ♪
♪ MMMBOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU BOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ MMMBOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU BOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU, YEAH ♪
♪ SAID OH YEAH ♪
♪ IN AN MMMBOP THEY'RE GONE ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ PLANT A SEED, PLANT A
FLOWER, PLANT A ROSE ♪
♪ YOU CAN PLANT
ANY ONE OF THOSE ♪
♪ KEEP PLANTING TO FIND
OUT WHICH ONE GROWS ♪
♪ IT'S A SECRET NO ONE KNOWS ♪
♪ OH, NO ONE KNOWS ♪
♪ MMMBOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU BOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU, YEAH ♪
♪ MMMBOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU BOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU, YEAH ♪
♪ IN A MMMBOP THEY'RE GONE ♪
♪ IN AN MMMBOP
THEY'RE NOT THERE ♪
♪ IN AN MMMBOP THEY'RE GONE ♪
♪ IN AN MMMBOP
THEY'RE NOT THERE ♪
♪ CAN YOU SAY YOU
LOSE YOU HAIR ♪
♪ OH, BUT YOU DON'T CARE ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ MMMBOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU BOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU, YEAH ♪
♪ MMMBOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU BOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU, YEAH ♪
♪ CAN YOU TELL ME, OH ♪
♪ NO, YOU CAN'T 'CAUSE
YOU DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ CAN YOU TELL ME, OH YEAH ♪
♪ YOU SAY YOU CAN
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ CAN YOU TELL ME, OH ♪
♪ WHICH FLOWER'S GOING TO GROW ♪
♪ NO, YOU CAN'T 'CAUSE
YOU DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ CAN YOU TELL ME ♪
♪ IF IT'S GONNA BE
A DAISY OR A ROSE ♪
♪ YOU SAY YOU CAN
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ SAY YOU CAN BUT
YOU DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ YOU DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ MMMBOP ♪
♪ DU BA ♪
♪ DU ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ MMMBOP ♪
♪ OH YEAH ♪
♪ DU BA ♪
♪ DU ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ MMMBOP, BA DUBA BOP ♪
♪ BA DU BOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU, YEAH ♪
♪ MMMBOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU BOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU, OH ♪
♪ MMMBOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU BOP, BA DUBA DOP ♪
♪ BA DU, OH ♪
♪ MMMBOP, BA DUBA BOP BA DU ♪